This regular meeting of the Miami Special Utility Authority for today's date, we have tonight to give me a reason.
Education pastor at First Christian Church Brian David Browns?
That is pretty heavy-fought in just pause two bring our focus and upon you
And further I pray that you would be with these men and women
That have given up their time to serve this community.
But, a prayer she'd grant them wisdom of the Father
And pray that you would just bless their decisions.
Father I also prayed, and blessed her family is the give this time to
The community which pulls them away from your families
So further we ask for special blessing upon
Their Family during these times of separation
And again, Father we ask for your wisdom. We asked you our insight to be upon this board
Father I love You and praise Your. It's in Jesus' name my prayer
Amen
Thank God
Congratulations
To the flag of United States America
And to the Republic for which it stands one nation under this will, there are T. and justice for all
Thank You
I have a number four is
Father Henry for an unscheduled personal approaches
Anyone in audience at Wichita address accounts on any of The Agenda
They're being known out upon his consent agenda
Staffers recommending items six-and seven for
The consent agenda
There are no questions either.
Motion for a minute
Second
Joseph
Fourth sir
Hi
I am eight author of the experience that have automatic transfer switch
For Walmart, it will transfer power between Feature 22 and 29
And the case in Outreach
Not to exceed 65 thousand
You know Tyler, I'm going to kind of take you.
At the end
Our last council meeting
Council in Lester had pointed out that on Christmas day
That Walmart experience managed
And art staff was very quickly
To care about it and
Appreciate
Work with a question wasn't there
A switch
It's supposed
To be a good idea
And after the meeting
Tyler and I got on that
Finally, as was also in 12 with this
Because
We understand from utilities
Without your knowledge
That project is basically killed
It's not not done
We've gone through some transitions
But what I'm trying to do is pick up the pieces from there and continue forward
On point out with Alicia's help
She gave me a agenda item was
And this would have been on July 3rd
What provided you
Was report for David Roundtree
Also, from Jeff Bishop
About
If they had power
And if it's in excess of five
Seconds, they have to reset everything
Of the store empty
The stores and at basically
Effects their operations
Empting a storage that large plus
That was
That is what I'm saying
But
At this time
It worked with Tyler
What do you understand about
And I think it was trying to say some money
There were a discussion about
Trying build one of these
In fact, even in what's given
He used to do something
Something along that line
That doesn't make me feel real comfortable with the idea
Building like this
The best thing is
To go out and buy something
It has been tested as warranties
And we'll handle things
Not only handled the transfer
Handle of switches when they're necessary
But also it's for the safety
Of our employees as well to make sure that something like this is built properly
So Brian, excuse me Tyler has been working on
In essence
He said a little bit research
We think in a new switch
We have a lot of money
And I understand that
But it's something the council had
Talked about doing in past
It is
And it also ties into the fact that
I don't think we should be looking at this and
This is not only improvement
That would make our utility system
We were talking before
Before meeting started,
It was called a
Necal Substation
The Rogers Practice field
That's one that was installed in the early 1970s
Has had some maintenance work but not a whole lot
And really needs to be rebuilt
To improve this electrical service
Something like
It is currently working on kind of an overall plan for improvements
In our electrical system
Just doing it
Water System and sewer system
But since this was an item that the council had identified
And really improved just three years and I have less than 3
Years ago, frankly
Something it is promised to one of our businesses
It's something
That has never been necessary for their operations
So we want a proceed with providing
Providing you in getting approval so
We can move on
Definitely my recommendation
We will be able to do this
I want you
To improve the system
We are going
To bring it
I also highlight that our utility rates we have improved
We're approved with
The idea of some projects
There was one question about where the specific line item will come out of
And we have a one item, one line item in our budget for
About 93 thousand dollars which is overhead lines
So it'll be taking this expense
We're keeping an eye on
Our new revenue coming into our new rates just went
To affect and seeing if that brings some additional revenue
This probably something
That were playing little catch up
Provided to you but I also feel very comfortable that we are doing it right
And what is being proposed by us
Doing an in a write manner
So thats why they will be recommending approval
I have
Tell on this with the generator
That Dana had mentioned
You possibly'll
Have put into effect
What businesses going
To do?
The issue of discount amount
You're not going to be showing power off
Anybody else?
No, this is purely a circle
With the type situation you are looking at other areas that could
Underthe same types
Have we
This about only one so far
That were up against
What they dealing with right now
Is an item for your reactive
But what need
So in our system we need to be a problem
Not just two are commercial areas
Even some of us service areas
We have discussions around the hospital
About improving electrical services
And it is something that's long overdue
That you do
Have resources
To deal with
To have Tyler over a smaller organization
Because an absolutely no offense to Joe
He did it great job when he was public or extrector
But we needed somebody
We need some focus on our utilities
It is just huge amount of infrastructure that
That make sure they are taken care of properly
I want Clara by something
Brian used the term generator
General, we put in a switch
We need to have a temporary generator
When we switch everything over
But just for that particular time
Just don't know what you are saying on the path
No, not all of them
That's it
I had one more question
And i'm not going put in my own spot
The loss
Of sales tax revenue per minute
At Walmart and
The numbers are still available
It is pretty significant
And that's one of the reasons we decided to have that
I don't think it was a spot
He will be less significant
But again i
Think were keeping a promise
That had been made by the way
With your question
Do you want to go on item eight
A promotion
Second
Hi
Johnson
Thank you
Thanks to our item nine new business
And the name or
This agenda
Staff reports on your package
I have questions
Trusting community announcements
On this one
It's a couple of ways
Going up to our utility department
My fact i called being not after this
Hasn't it?
I was up on the work and I came to my morning coffee
And you look at me now
Called Joe
Think Joe is in there somewhere
One year or so
Anyway he come back
He came back on that
What about, you know, what do your friends say about Tom McAll-Jell
You know, they didn't have to know
It's time I got that back on
That is pretty amazing stuff
Come in tomorrow now. Thank you
Is it the bill not show?
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Okay
Any other announcements
If there are nine out of twelve there will be a motion
Do John do you want most two adjourn
Second
Thank you